让我们来点击这个绿色的运行按钮
And now for the moment you've been waiting for, let's hit this green Run button.
它会让我们选择一个设备，因为我们没有物理设备
It will prompt us to choose a device, without a physical device we
所以用对应SDK版本的模拟器来测试App
can test the app using the emulator that comes with the Android SDK.
你应该在配置Android Studio时就已经创建了
An Android virtual device should have already been created for
一个Android虚拟设备
you automatically when you set up Android Studio.
所以单击OK
So you can go ahead and click OK.
在模拟器启动的这段时间里
While the emulator's booting up,
我想来介绍下怎样修改你的模拟设备
I want to point out that if you ever want to modify your emulator devices,
你可以点击这个紫色的按钮
you can click on this button with the purple device and the Android, and
打开AVD管理器来管理你的Android虚拟设备
open up the AVD manager to manage your Android virtual devices.
它列出了已存在的设备
It lists out your existing devices, and
你也可以新建其它的虚拟设备
you can always create another virtual device.
你可以选择设备的类别，然后选择一个特定设备
You can select the category of device and then a specific device.
然后需要选择运行的平台版本
Then you choose which platform version it should be running on.
这是这台电脑上唯一可运行的版本
And this is the only one that's available on this computer now.
所以我们选择Lollipop，选择target为Google API
So Lollipop is good, and we choose the Google API's target, because it
因为这会包括进去一些模拟器上已经预装好的Google服务
will include some Google services already pre-installed on the emulator.
选择Next
You can choose Next.
这里有更多可以自定义的选项和设置
There's a couple more options and settings that you can modify, for example,
例如，如果你想要添加一个SD卡，或者相机，你可以在这里选择
if you want an SD card, or a camera you can change those here, and
然后点击Finish，就创建了一个新的虚拟设备
then you can go ahead and click Finish, and it'll create a new AVD for you.